{
	"moviebluff": [
        {
            "Question": "A Boy and His Dog",
            "Answer": "A Man Communicates Telephathically With His Dog Who Can Sense The Presence Of Human Females",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Fish Tale",
            "Answer": "A Cartoon About Three Children Who Are Accidentally Turned Into Fish After Drinking A Scientist’s Potion",
        },
        {
            "Question": "A Report on the Party and Guests",
            "Answer": "A Group Of Picnickers Are Kidnapped And Taken To A Party",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Abbott and Costello Go to Mars",
            "Answer": "Two Men Launch A Rocket Headed For Mars That Instead Flies Them To New Orleans For Mardi Gras",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Acne",
            "Answer": "A Teenager Drinks Some Contaminated Water And His Head Becomes A Giant Pimple",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Allegro non Troppo",
            "Answer": "A Filmmaker Decides To Make His Own Version Of Fantasia Using An Orchestra Of Old Ladies Kept In A Dungeon",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Angel Unchained",
            "Answer": "A Biker Gang Teams Up With A Group Of Hippies To Defeat A Group Of Buggy-riding Ranchers",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Anne B. Real",
            "Answer": "A Rap Star Finds Her Voice With Help From The Diary Of Anne Frank",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Arizona Dream",
            "Answer": "A Man Meets A Rich Woman In Arizona Who Likes To Play The Accordion For Her Pet Turtles",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Ass Backwards",
            "Answer": "Two Grown Women Visit Their Hometown With Hopes Of Winning A Beauty Pageant They Lost As Kids",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Attack of the Killer Refrigerator",
            "Answer": "A Refrigerator Gets Even After Being Abused By A Group Of Partying Teenagers",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Bad Boy Bubby",
            "Answer": "A Man, Who Has Spent Thirty Years Tricked By His Mother Into Staying Inside A Small Room, Escapes",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Basket Case",
            "Answer": "\ra Man Carries Around A Basket Holding His Once Conjoined Twin Brother, Looking For The Doctors Who Separated Them Against Their Will",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Battlefield Earth",
            "Answer": "Earth Is Under The Rule Of An Alien Race That Tries To Force The Surviving Humans To Be Gold Miners",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Bill and Coo",
            "Answer": "A Town Of Birds Are Terrorized By An Evil Raven",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Blind Beast",
            "Answer": "A Blind Sculptor And His Mother Kidnap A Young Model",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Bliss",
            "Answer": "A Man Dies And Goes To Hell To Find That Everything Is The Same As It Was On Earth",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Blue Monkey",
            "Answer": "A Hospital Is Attacked By A Parasitic Worm That Grows Into A Huge Problem",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Body in the Web",
            "Answer": "Survivors Of A Plane Crash Find Themselves On An Island Covered By Spiders Whose Bites Turn Them Into Spiders",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Breakin’ 2: Electric Boogaloo",
            "Answer": "Local Breakdancers Try To Stop The Community Recreation Center From Being Bulldozed By Developers",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Breaking Wind",
            "Answer": "A Comedic Spoof Of The Twilight Saga",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Bubba Ho-Tep",
            "Answer": "Elvis And Jfk Battle An Ancient Egyptian Mummy To Save Their Nursing Homes",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Bush Christmas",
            "Answer": "Four Australian Children In The Outback Change Their Christmas Plans When A Group Of Outlaws Steal Their Father’s Horses",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Buttwhistle",
            "Answer": "A College Student Stops A Woman’s Suicide Effort, And She Seeks Revenge",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Bye Bye Monkey",
            "Answer": "A Man Finds King Kong’s Body On The Beach In New York And Decides To Raise His Orphaned Son",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Carry on Matron",
            "Answer": "A Group Of Thieves Plans To Make A Fortune Stealing Birth Control Pills From A Maternity Hospital",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Carry on Screaming!",
            "Answer": "An Evil Doctor Kidnaps Beautiful Women And Turns Them Into Mannequins To Sell To Local Stores",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Chained for Life",
            "Answer": "A Conjoined Twin Kills Her Husband, And The Courts Aren’t Sure How To Sentence Her Without Punishing Her Sister, Who Had Nothing To Do With It",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Chasing the Kidney Stone",
            "Answer": "A Young Boy Joins The Other Children Living Inside His Grandfather’s Body To Fight A Kidney Stone",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Cinderella 2000",
            "Answer": "In A Futuristic World Where Big Brother Knows Everything, A Girl Tries To Find A Way To Be With The Man She Loves",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Cloudburst",
            "Answer": "A Lesbian Couple Escapes Their Nursing Home To Get Married In Canada, Picking Up A Hitchhiker Along The Way",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Companions in Nightmare",
            "Answer": "One Of The Patients In A Therapy Group Ends Up Being A Murderer",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Cool as Ice",
            "Answer": "Vanilla Ice Assumes The Role Of Marlon Brando In This Remake",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Cool Cat Saves the Kids",
            "Answer": "A Kid’s Anti-bullying Movie About Cool Cat, The Coolest Cat In The World, And Butch The Bully Who Hates Him For It",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Creating Rem Lazar",
            "Answer": "A Musical About Two Kids Who Create An Imaginary Superhero Friend",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Creep Van",
            "Answer": "A Man Thinks He Got A Good Deal On A Van That Turns Out To Be Booby-trapped And Tries To Kill Him",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Cupcakes",
            "Answer": "Six Friends Record A Song On Impulse, Bringing Unexpected Overnight Stardom",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Dance with Me, Henry",
            "Answer": "Two Goofy Men Attempt To Run An Old Amusement Park",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Danny Deckchair",
            "Answer": "A Truck Driver Who Is Bored With His Life Decides To Escape By Tying Helium-filled Balloons To His Deck Chair And Floating Away",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Dead Ringers",
            "Answer": "Twin Gynecologists Enjoy The Fact That No One Can Tell Them Apart Until They Fall For The Same Woman",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Death Bed -The Bed That Eats",
            "Answer": "A Tree Falls In Love With A Woman And Turns Himself Into A Bed For Her To Sleep On",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Demon Island",
            "Answer": "Teens Trapped On An Island Are Haunted By A Demon Hidden Inside A Piata",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Die-ner (Get It?)",
            "Answer": "A Killer Attacks A Diner Staff Who Come Back To Life As Zombies",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Doggiewoggiez! Poochiewoochiez!",
            "Answer": "A Surrealist Film Composed Entirely Of Borrowed Clips Of Dog Films",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Dogtooth",
            "Answer": "Three Teenagers Have Been Raised Without Ever Leaving Their House And Their Parents Say They Can Only Leave When Their Dogtooth Falls Out",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Dreamaniac",
            "Answer": "Heavy Metal Music Brings A Dead Woman Back To Life As An Evil Assasin",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Eegah",
            "Answer": "A Group Of Teenagers Run Into A Caveman Who Goes On A Rampage",
        },
        {
            "Question": "El Santos vs. La Tetona Mendoza",
            "Answer": "A Sad Fighter Starts A Business That Expoloits A Recent Zombie Invasion To Forget His Breakup With A Sexy Wrestler",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Electrick Children",
            "Answer": "A Mormon Teen Believes She’s Become Pregnant By Listening To Music And Sets Out To Find The Father",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Elevator Movie",
            "Answer": "A Man And A Woman Get Stuck Inside An Elevator And Must Live There For Several Months.",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Enemy",
            "Answer": "A Man Searches For His Doppleganger After Seeing Him In A Movie",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Exte: Hair Extensions",
            "Answer": "A Horror Movie About Hair Extensions That Attack The Women That Wear Them",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Eyes Without a Face",
            "Answer": "A Famous Surgeon’s Daughter Is In A Car Crash And He Tries To Fix Her Face By Stealing The Faces Of Other Women",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Fah",
            "Answer": "A Cop Struggles To Capture A Gang Of Jewelry Thieves Who Have His Fiancee Held Hostage",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Fantastic Planet",
            "Answer": "Set In The Future On A Planet Far Away, Humans Are Kept As Pets By Giant Blue Aliens",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Flying Devils",
            "Answer": "A Family Of Aerialists Decides To Compete For A Big Prize Offered For Performing A Nearly Impossible Trapeze Stunt",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Forbidden Zone",
            "Answer": "A Musical Tale Of A Girl Who Finds A Gateway To Another Dimension In Her Family’s Basement",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Frankenhood",
            "Answer": "Two Morticians Use A Reanimated Corpse To Help Them Win A Streetball Tournament",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Gang of Ghosts",
            "Answer": "A Group Of Ghosts From Various Backgrounds Lose Their Shelter Due To Urbanization",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Garbage",
            "Answer": "Two Garbage Truck Drivers In Hollywood Find Missing Oscars And Become Instant Celebrities",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Git Gob",
            "Answer": "A Short Film About Two Creature Things Arguing About Whether Their Discovery Is A Hat Or A Hole In The Ground",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Good Boy, Bad Boy",
            "Answer": "Two College Students With Identical Names Exchange Their Classes",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Gor",
            "Answer": "An Adult Fairy Tale About A Professor Who Is Transported To A New World Where He Falls In Love With A Barbarian Princess",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Greedy Guts",
            "Answer": "A Married Couple Adopts A Piece Of Carved Wood In The Backyard As Their Child, Which Comes To Life And Becomes Evil",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Gudia",
            "Answer": "Bollywood Film About A Ventriloquist Who Loses His Voice And Asks His Student To Take Control Of His Talking Doll For The Show",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Gummo",
            "Answer": "Lonely Residents Of A Tornado-stricken Town In Ohio Wander Around Trying To Find Fulfillment In Their Boring Lives",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Gumshoe",
            "Answer": "A Bingo Caller Longs For A Change Of Career And Advertsises Himself As A Private Eye In The Local Newspaper",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Hercules in New York",
            "Answer": "Hercules, Played By Arnold Schwarzenegger, Finds True Love On Earth And Starts A Career In Bodybuilding",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Holy Motors",
            "Answer": "A Man Drives Around Paris And Takes On Various Roles, Leading Him To Become An Accordion Player, Hitman And Leprechaun",
        },
        {
            "Question": "House",
            "Answer": "Seven Girls Visit A Possessed House That Plans To Eat Them",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Howard the Duck",
            "Answer": "A 27 Year Old Punk Duck Is Sent On A Mission To Ohio Where He Applies For A Job As A Janitor And Joins A Rock Band While Looking For A Way Back To His Planet",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Humpty Sharma Ki Dulhania",
            "Answer": "A Girl Makes A Trip To Delhi For Her Marriage Shopping Where She Meets A Cute And Carefree Guy At A Bookstore",
        },
        {
            "Question": "I Accuse My Parents",
            "Answer": "A Young Man Works For Gangsters To Try And Impress His Nightclub-singer Girlfriend",
        },
        {
            "Question": "I Married a Strange Person!",
            "Answer": "A Man Develops A Lump On His Neck That Gives Him The Power To Transform People And Objects At Will, His Wife Is Very Upset",
        },
        {
            "Question": "If I Were You",
            "Answer": "In A Plot To Get Revenge On Her Cheating Husband, A Wife Is Forced To Star As King Lear In A Wonderfully Horrible Production",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Inauguration of the Pleasure Dome",
            "Answer": "A Short Film About Historical, Biblical, And Mythical Creatures That Gather Together In A Pleasure Dome",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Inkheart",
            "Answer": "A Girl Discovers Her Father Can Bring Characters In Books To Life And Must Stop A Villain From Destroying Them",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Into the West",
            "Answer": "Two Young Irish Brothers Head Out On An Adventure To Rescue Their White Stallion From The Hands Of An Unethical Horse Breeder",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Iron Sky",
            "Answer": "The Remainder Of The Third Reich Is Living On The Moon, Plotting Their Return To Earth To Conquer America",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Ishtar",
            "Answer": "Two Songwriters Who Dream Of Making It Big Are Booked As Lounge Singers In Morocco And Become Involved In A Plot To Overthrow The Goverment Of A Fictional Country",
        },
        {
            "Question": "It’s Alive",
            "Answer": "A Couple Have A Baby But It Turns Out To Be A Monster Who Kills When It’s Scared",
        },
        {
            "Question": "John Dies at the End",
            "Answer": "A Drug Called ‘soy Sauce’ Allows Two College Dropouts To See An Imminent And Dangerous Alien Invasion",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Julie and Jack",
            "Answer": "A Computer Chip Salesman And A Software Designer Meet And Fall In Love Inside A Virtual Reality Program",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Kambakkht Ishq",
            "Answer": "An Indian Stuntman Finds Success In Hollwyood But Can’t Find Love",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Key of Life",
            "Answer": "A Comedy About A Struggling Actor Who Takes Advantage Of A Hitman With Amnesia By Trading Lives With Him",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Kumiko, the Treasure Hunter",
            "Answer": "A Japanese Woman Finds A Copy Of The Movie Fargo And Thinks It’s A Real Life Treasure Map And Decides To Travel To America To Find The Money",
        },
        {
            "Question": "L’iceburg",
            "Answer": "A Fast-food Manager Gets Locked Overnight In A Walk-in Freezer And Becomes Obsessed With All Things Icy And Cold",
        },
        {
            "Question": "La Cama",
            "Answer": "Three Beds Tell Their Stories In This Mexican Comedy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Laserblast",
            "Answer": "A Teen Finds An Alien Weapon And Is Transformed Into A Killer",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Legend of the Shadowy Ninja: The Ninja Dragon",
            "Answer": "A Secret Ninja Dragon Attempts To Kill Jabba The Hutt And Save His Love, But Jabba Turns Into A Massive Zombie Turkey",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Lolo",
            "Answer": "A Boy Who Believes He Was Conceived From An Italian Tomato Tries To Make Sense Of His Life",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Life Is Cheap… But Toilet Paper is Expensive",
            "Answer": "A Man Faces Some Trouble When He Is Hired To Take A Briefcase From America To Hong Kong",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Liquid Sky",
            "Answer": "Invisible Aliens Searching For Heroin Land On Top Of An Apartment In New York",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Little Big Top",
            "Answer": "A Depressed And Aging Clown Finds Passion When He Returns Home To Teach Amateur Clowns",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Maelstrom",
            "Answer": "The Story Of A Pretty Young Socialite Whose Life Is In Shambles, Narrated By A Talking Fish",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Manos: the Hands of Fate",
            "Answer": "A Family Gets Lost On The Road And Stumbles Upon A Hidden Devil-worshipping Cult",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Martin",
            "Answer": "A Man Believes He Is A Vampire And Tries To Stop Himself By Moving To A Small Town To Live With His Cousin",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Matango",
            "Answer": "Survivors Of A Shipwreck Turn In To Mushrooms",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Meat Love",
            "Answer": "A Short Film In Which Two Pieces Of Meat Fall In Love",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Mental",
            "Answer": "A Man Finds And Hires A Nanny On The Side Of The Road To Take Care Of His Five Daughters",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Mere Brother Ki Dulhan",
            "Answer": "A Bollywood Film Producer Sets Out To Find A Bride For His Brother, But Falls In Love With Her Himself",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Mermaid in a Manhole",
            "Answer": "A Horror Film About An Artist Who Finds A Mermaid In The Sewer And Rescues Her",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Mesa of Lost Women",
            "Answer": "A Crazy Scientist Wants To Create A Race Of Superwomen By Injecting Female Subjects With Spider Venom",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Miami Connection",
            "Answer": "A Group Of Motorcylce-riding Ninjas Stop A Cocaine Deal In Miami, Taking The Drugs Back To Orlando To Party",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Miss Granny",
            "Answer": "After Learning She’s Being Sent To A Nursing Home, A Woman Goes For A Walk And Finds A Photo Studio Where She Emerges As A 20-year-old",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Mood Indigo",
            "Answer": "A Wealthy Man Tries To Find A Cure For His Lover Who Has A Flower Growing In Her Lungs",
        },
        {
            "Question": "My Heart Belongs to Bonzo",
            "Answer": "A Splinter Puts A Girl In A Coma, And A Boy Gets Turned Into A Half-ape Killer",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Naked Lunch",
            "Answer": "An Exterminator Becomes Addicted To The Substance He Uses To Kill Bugs And Accidentally Murders His Wife",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Nico the Unicorn",
            "Answer": "A Young Boy’s Father Passes Away And His Life Is Changed When The Pony He Rescues Gives Birth To A Unicorn",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Night Train to Terror",
            "Answer": "God And Satan Discuss The Fate Of Three Humans And Watch Bad Horror Films On A Train",
        },
        {
            "Question": "O Lucky Man!",
            "Answer": "A Surrealist Musical Following The Adventures Of A Coffee Salesman In Europe",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Oh My God",
            "Answer": "A Shopkeeper In Mumbai Files A Lawsuit Against God For The Earthquake That Destroyed His Store",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Paintball",
            "Answer": "Things Take A Bad Turn When A Player Brings A Real Gun To A Paintball Match",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Paprika",
            "Answer": "A Machine That Allows Therapists To Enter Patients’ Dreams Is Stolen",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Pastorela",
            "Answer": "A Cop Battles A New Pastor Who Changed The Casting In The Holiday Play",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Phase IV",
            "Answer": "Desert Ants Plot To Rule The World And Begin Killing Humans In Their Path",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Phffft",
            "Answer": "A Couple Gets Divorced But Find That They Miss Each Other And Dance The Mambo",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Phil the Alien",
            "Answer": "An Alien Named Phil Gets Stranded In Ontario Where He Starts Drinking And Befriends A Talking Beaver",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Picnic at Hanging Rock",
            "Answer": "A Teacher And Some Students At An All Girl’s School Disappear From A Picnic",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Pocket Ninjas",
            "Answer": "Three Teenagers Must Stop The An Evil Being From Polluting The Environment",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Popstar",
            "Answer": "A Girl Learns That Her New Friend Is A Pop Star And Her Life Is Turned Upside Down",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Pup",
            "Answer": "A Sheepdog Wants To Prove He’s The Best Ever By Flying To The Moon",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Rabid Grannies",
            "Answer": "A Kid Gives His Grandparents A Gift That Turns Them Into Killer Demons",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Rat Pfink a Boo Boo",
            "Answer": "A Woman Is Kidnapped So Her Friend And Gardner Decide To Put On Costumes And Become Superheroes To Save Her",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Ricky",
            "Answer": "Katie And Paco Fall In Love And Give Birth To A Baby Boy That Grows Wings",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Robot Monster",
            "Answer": "A Gorilla Alien In A Helmet Invades A Canyon With His Bubble Machine",
        },
        {
            "Question": "RRRrrrr!!!",
            "Answer": "The Tribe Of The Dirty Hairs Must Fight The Tribe Of The Clean Hairs For Access To Shampoo",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Rubber",
            "Answer": "A Killer Car Tire Visits A Desert Town",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Santa and the Ice Cream Bunny",
            "Answer": "Santa’s Sleigh Gets Stuck In Florida And He Tells A Group Of Kids The Story Of Thumbelina",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Santa Claus Conquers the Martians",
            "Answer": "Some Martians Kidnap Santa And Bring Him To Mars Because They Need Someone To Give Presents To Their Children",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Santa with Muscles",
            "Answer": "A Corrupt Millionaire Gets Amnesia And Believes He Is Santa",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Say Ahh…",
            "Answer": "Two Doctors Who Are Also Brothers Fall For The Same Mother Of One Of Their Patients",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Sir Billi",
            "Answer": "A Retired Veterinarian Meets A Goat Who Thinks He’s A Dog, And A Beaver Who Was Raised By Rabbits",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Six-String Samurai",
            "Answer": "A Rock ‘n’ Roll Samurai Takes A Young Boy Under His Protection",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Sssssss",
            "Answer": "A College Student Gets A Job As A Lab Assistant For A Doctor Who Secretly Plans To Turn Him Into A Snake",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Starbuck",
            "Answer": "The Life Of A Forty-something Slacker Changes When He Finds Out His Sperm Donations Have Resulted In Over 500 Children",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Strange Frame: Love u0026 Sax",
            "Answer": "An Animated Lesbian Science Fiction Musical Set On The Moons Of Jupiter",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Suspiria",
            "Answer": "A Fairy Tale About Witches Who Operate A Ballet Academy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Take It Big",
            "Answer": "A Man Who Plays The \”bottom Half\” Of A Horse In A Comedy Act Inherets A Ranch",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Taking 5",
            "Answer": "Two Nerdy Teens Kidnap A Famous Boy-band Hoping To Get Them To Play At Their High School To Become More Popular",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Tees Maar Khan",
            "Answer": "A Man Pretends He Is A Movie Producer And Tries To Trick An Entire Village Into Helping Him Rob A Train For Treasure",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Tetsuo, the Iron Man",
            "Answer": "A Man Has An Insane Compulsion To Stick Scrap Metal Into His Body",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The 5,000 Fingers of Dr. T",
            "Answer": "A Crazy Doctor Forces 500 Boys To Practice On A Giant Piano Around The Clock In This Musical With Lyrics By Dr. Seuss",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Adventures of Buckaroo Banzai Across the 8th Dimension",
            "Answer": "A Rock Musician Surgeon And His Gang Take On Evil Aliens From The 8th Dimension",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Apple",
            "Answer": "A Disco Rock Opera About A Pair Of Young Singers Who Sign Onto A Music Label But Find It Is Corrupt",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Beast of Yucca Flats",
            "Answer": "A Soviet Scientist Is Hit By A Nuclear Explosion And Turns Into A Beast",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Beast with a Million Eyes",
            "Answer": "An Alien With The Ability To Inhabit Anything That’s Alive Can Only Be Stopped By A Family’s Love",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Benchwarmers",
            "Answer": "Three Grown Men Form A Baseball Team And Compete Against Children’s Leagues",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Big Feast",
            "Answer": "A Group Of Men Hire A Group Of Prostitutes To Go With Them To The Countryside Where They Decide To Eat Themselves To Death",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Blood of a Poet",
            "Answer": "An Artist Draws A Face On An Easel And It Comes To Life",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Blue Bird",
            "Answer": "A Pair Of Children Are Led By A Fairy On A Magical Quest For The Bluebird Of Happiness",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Dark Backward",
            "Answer": "A Garbage Man Encourages His Friend To Pursue Stand-up Comedy, But He’s Only Successful Once He\rgrows A Third Arm Out Of His Back",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Discreet Charm of the Bourgeoisie",
            "Answer": "A Plotless Series Of Dreams About Six Middle-class People And Their Attempts To Have A Meal Together",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Englishman Who Went Up a Hill But Came Down a Mountain",
            "Answer": "A Community Is Very Offended When An English Mapmaker Informs Them That Their Mountain Is Only A Hill",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Exterminating Angel",
            "Answer": "Guests At An Upper-class Dinner Party Find Themselves Unable To Leave",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The FP",
            "Answer": "Rival Gangs Fight For Control Of A Park By Playing A Deadly Version Of Dance, Dance, Revolution",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Future",
            "Answer": "A Stray Cat Saves A Failing Relationship",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Ghost in the Invisible Bikini",
            "Answer": "A Corpse Has 24 Hours To Do A Good Deed In Exchange For Having His Youth Restored",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Hands of Orlac",
            "Answer": "A Man Loses Both Hands, And New, Murderous Ones, Are Attached",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Idiot of the Mountains",
            "Answer": "An Man Gets The Police To Save A Kidnapped Girl And Is Cured Of Being An Idiot",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Immaculate Conception of Little Dizzle",
            "Answer": "A Man Takes A Night Gig As A Janitor And Learns That The Company Is Experimenting On The Janitors",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Kingdom of Crooked Mirrors",
            "Answer": "A Frog Competes In The World’s First Corn Dog And Lasagna Eating Contest",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Last Starfighter",
            "Answer": "A Boy Living In A Trailer Park Is Obsessed With Video Games And Finds Himself Recruited For A Real Life Alien Defense Force",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Legend of the Titanic",
            "Answer": "A Mouse Tells His Grandchildren The Real Story Of The Titanic That Includes Himself, Evil Sharks, And A Giant Octopus",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Man Who Loved Cat Dancing",
            "Answer": "A Wife Leaves Her Husband To Join Some Western Outlaws",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Perils of Gwendoline in the Land of the Yik Yak",
            "Answer": "A Woman Travels To China In A Box On A Mission To Find Her Father Who Was Last Seen Searching For A Butterfly",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Phone Box",
            "Answer": "A Man Gets Trapped Inside A Telephone Box And No One Is Able To Free Him",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Puffy Chair",
            "Answer": "A Man Drives Cross-country On A Mission To Deliver A Giant Purple Lazyboy To His Father",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Red Squirrel",
            "Answer": "A Suicidal Man Pretends To Be The Boyfriend Of A Gorgeous Amnesia Victim",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Serpent and the Rainbow",
            "Answer": "An Anthropologist Visits Haiti To Learn How To Turn People Into Zombies",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Thing with Two Heads",
            "Answer": "A White Racist’s Head Is Transplated Onto The Body Of A Black Man",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Toxic Avenger",
            "Answer": "A Bullied Nerd Gets Dropped Into Nuclear Waste That Turns Him Into A Crime-fighting Monster Who Falls In Love",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Voices",
            "Answer": "A Man Pursues His Office Crush With Help From His Evil Talking Pets",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Theodore Rex",
            "Answer": "A Female Detective Is Paired With A Talking Dinosaur To Investigate The Killing Of All The Dinosaurs",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Things",
            "Answer": "A Man Who Wants Children Convinces His Wife To Undergo An Experiment Which Results In The Birth Of Many Non-human Things",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Tom Yum Goong",
            "Answer": "A Young Fighter Travels To Australia To Find His Stolen Elephant",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Torremolinos 73",
            "Answer": "An Encyclopedia Salesman Sees Opportunity For Change When He And His Wife Are Asked To Star In A Series Of Educational Erotic Films",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Trail of the Screaming Forehead",
            "Answer": "A Small Town Is Invaded By Crawling Foreheads That Begin Attaching Themselves To People",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Treevenge",
            "Answer": "Christmas Trees Plan Revenge For Being Ripped Out Of The Forest",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Uninvited",
            "Answer": "A Killer Cat Finds His Way On Board A Gangster’s Yacht Headed For A Caribbean Cruise",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Upstream Color",
            "Answer": "Thanks To A Mysterious Worm, A Psychic Link Is Formed Between A Woman And A Pig",
        },
        {
            "Question": "We Are the Best!",
            "Answer": "A Group Of 13-year-olds Refuse To Believe Punk Is Dead And Form A Band, Despite Their Lack Of Musical Talent",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Weekend",
            "Answer": "A Weekend Trip To The Countryside Turns Into A Never-ending Nightmare Of Traffic Jams",
        },
        {
            "Question": "White Pongo",
            "Answer": "Scientists Head Into The Jungle To Find An Albino Gorilla Who They Believe Is The Missing Link Between Man And Monkey",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Witching and Bitching",
            "Answer": "A Gang Of Jewelry Thieves On The Run Gets Caught And Trapped By A Group Of Witches",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Wrong Cops",
            "Answer": "The Crime Rate In Los Angeles Is At A Record-low, So Bored Cops Start Acting Like Criminals To Pass The Time",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Zaat",
            "Answer": "A Mad Nazi Scientist Turns Himself Into A Catfish",
        },
        {
            "Question": "ZsaZsa Zaturnnah Ze Moveeh",
            "Answer": "A Man Eats A Pink Rock That Turns Him Into A Beautiful Superheroine Whenever He Wants",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Zzzzzzz",
            "Answer": "A Short Film About A Couple In Love That Sleepwalks Through The City At Night",
        }
    ]
}